# MAT Busch

#### CONTACT



0413810616



mathewbusch2@gmail.com



mathewbusch.com

#### **EDUCATION**

University of Sydney Design Computing 2015 - 2018

#### SKILLS

#### Design

UX/UI design

Interaction design

Design Thinking

Sketch, Figma, InVision & Studio

Adobe CC & MC

InVision

#### Development

HTML, CSS, JS

React, Angular, jQuery, Bootstrap,

React Native, Gatsby

API's including Google Maps

#### ABOUT ME

I am a easy going light hearted guy who enjoys the challenge of taking complex user flows and turning them into simple user experiences through use of data.

I come from a strong broadcast and media centric background having worked on Live Broadcast graphics and now at an agency working on both Financial and Grocery services clients.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# Wunderman Thompson. Oct 2017 - Present Delivery Lead Optimisation Team

Utilising data to design, develop and personalise refreshing new expereinces that increase both UX and conversaions for Financial and Supermarket clients in both their website and application spaces.

# VPA Technologies. Nov 2015 - Sep 2016 Design and Development

Design and development of the company website. Media and content production for the site and clients. Camera operations and video editing.

### REFRENCES

Alice Leather - Manager Wunderman Thompson (0413975335)

Adam Burke - LIGR CTO (0402430658)

Goivanni Scaffidi - Senior Test and Personlisation - Suncorp (0402181637)